(Penny:)Well, here's your key.
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Enjoy having the place
to yourselves.
(Leonard:)You enjoy your mission to boldly
go where no man has gone before.
(Sheldon:)It's Penny's bedroom.
(Sheldon:)Plenty of men have gone before.
(Penny:)Now, now, there's no need
to make this emotional.
(Amy:)Shall we?
(Sheldon:)I guess this is it.
(Leonard:)You guys have fun.
(Sheldon:)You, too.
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't forget.
(Sheldon:)Tuesday the air filters
need to be changed.
(Penny:)Yeah, you wrote it on my hand.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and every other day,
(Sheldon:)check the water level
on the avocado pit.
(Leonard:)I'm on it.
(Leonard:)15 years from now, we'll
make guacamole together.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, please, let me go.
(Amy:)Come on, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Bye.
- Good night.